selfgrowthengine.com 2014-07-05

# Privacy Policy | Self Growth Engine

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our visitors, members and partners. It is designed not only to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, but also to help you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This Privacy Policy will be continually assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. 

This Privacy Policy shall apply to the following PlattForm Advertising, Inc. property: SelfGrowthEngine.com (collectively and individually hereinafter referred to as the "SelfGrowthEngine.com" "the Web site," or "the Site"). 

Access to and use of the SelfGrowthEngine.com web site is available only to United States residents who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. If you do not qualify, you may not use the Web site. If you are a minor, you may use the SelfGrowthEngine.com web site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult. We urge supervising adults to actively oversee minors' online use. 

As described below, some of your personally identifiable information will be used by us and shared with third parties. By using the Web site, you expressly consent to our use of your personal information, and also to the disclosure to and use of this information by third parties. You acknowledge that communications to, from and through the SelfGrowthEngine.com web site are not confidential. You agree that by submitting communications through the SelfGrowthEngine.com web site, no confidential, fiduciary, contractually implied, or other relationship is created between you and PlattForm Advertising, Inc. other than pursuant to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of our Terms and Conditions. 

### A Note About Minors

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, no one under 13 years of age can use the Web site. If you are a minor between the ages of 13 and 18, you may use the Site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

The goal of the SelfGrowthEngine.com web site is to be your favorite self improvement destination on the Internet by providing you with the information, services and product offerings that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, we collect two types of information from you when you visit the Site: personally identifiable information you voluntarily choose to disclose, and "aggregate information" about your use of the Site, which is automatically collected when you visit the Web site. 

  1. **Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are. Personal information is collected when you voluntarily choose to request information from a company that is listed on the Site. As a site user, you are asked to provide certain basic information such as your name, current e-mail address and programs of interest. You may also provide additional personal information at your discretion. Further, if you choose to correspond with us through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses. 

**How Do We Use The Personal Information That You Provide To Us?**

Broadly speaking, your personal information is used to help match your interests with companies that provide the self improvement services you seek. If your search yields no results, we may store your information and send you updates if and when programs you specified do become available. 

We also use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. 

  2. **Aggregate Information**

Aggregate information refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after the Web site) the date and time of your visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Web site, browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform), and IP (Internet Protocol) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. When you request a page from one of our Sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners, and for purposes of system administration. This allows these parties to advertise more effectively and allows you to receive advertisements that are most relevant to your personal interests. 

  3. **Cookies**

The SelfGrowthEngine.com web site, along with thousands of other web sites, uses standard technologies, such as cookies and web server logs to enhance your web viewing experience. Cookies and web server logs automatically track certain information about you that is based upon your activity on the Site. A cookie is a small piece of data transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site may track your activities on the site. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit the Web site and also to evaluate the Site's visitor capacity. 

Each time you access the Site, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookies. Cookies allow us to determine which areas and features of our Site are most popular by measuring user activity. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users as they move from one page to another. Cookies let sites and advertisers "remember" users across pages of a site and across multiple visits to a site. This allows e-commerce and Internet advertising to: personalize features such as targeted news stories, provide shopping sessions and quick navigation across multiple zones of e-commerce sites, remember user names and passwords for future visits, control ad frequency or the number of times a user sees a given ad, and deliver advertisements targeted to a user's interests. Your computer may occasionally receive cookies from our advertisers. PlattForm Advertising, Inc. does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to our Privacy Policy. You can disable cookies, but access to certain parts of the Web site may no longer be available to you. 

### Sharing Information With Co-Brand Service Providers

PlattForm Advertising, Inc. offers a number of third party services from the Site. If you choose to use these optional services, we may provide some of your personally identifiable information to the Co-Brand Service Provider offering such services. Conversely, the Co-Brand Service Provider may provide PlattForm Advertising, Inc. with personal information about you. 

### Sharing Information With Affiliated Businesses, Strategic Partners, Subsidiaries, Advertisers, And Other Third Parties

We may enter into strategic marketing alliances with third parties, such as advertisers, businesses, strategic partners and subsidiaries, who may be given access to personal information, including your name, address and e-mail, for the purpose of providing you with information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisers and other third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit the Site. PlattForm Advertising, Inc. has no control over what third parties do with this information. Further, we cannot and do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. 

### Information Collected In Ad Delivery 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

### Notice Of New Services And Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. 

### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect. This software provides a limited degree of protection against unauthorized access or disclosure, as well as accidental loss, alteration or destruction. 

### Do We Comply With Legally Compelled Disclosure Of Information?

We may release any private information about you that we possess when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy and/or other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of PlattForm Advertising, Inc., the Site users, or others. 

### What About Other Web Sites Linked To Or From The Web Site?

The links in the SelfGrowthEngine.com web site allow you to leave the Site. Please be aware that once you leave the Site and enter another web site, or use certain services provided through the Site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on web sites that have a link to the Web site, or any links contained in a linked site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. PlattForm Advertising, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by these sites, nor the information or content contained therein. We provide these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by PlattForm Advertising, Inc. of the site. Please read over the rules and policies of these sites before proceeding. 

### Tell A Friend

We take the privacy of our users very seriously, and as such, no information from the Tell-a-Friend link is logged at any time. Tell-a-Friend is a referral service in which e-mail addresses are used only to send this one-time message. The e-mail addresses are then automatically wiped from our system, and neither e-mail addresses nor names of either party are kept, stored or sold at any time. The e-mail sent is immediate, the information is not passed along to our server, and no data is kept for comparison purposes. Because of this, it is possible to receive more than one e-mail from our site, and we apologize for any inconvenience this may cause.
